[Music]
there are a few foundational pillars
that we focused on as a company
the number one absolute number one has
been building consumer trust number two
you know leadership for what I mean
leadership not just from a top line
perspective but it has to be more
sustainable yeah so focus on risk
management focus on all other aspects of
business rather than just Top Line I
think that's that's important third
thing is that we believe we've tried to
stay invested and you know kind of
invested ahead of the time on uh Tech
but you know and this is not just now
over the years we've always been focused
on declarative Innovation yeah and
that's helped us and underpinning all of
this is I think a usual issue of people
and culture
foreign
[Music]